tweezerman.com 2018-09-08

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy last updated January 29, 2016.

Our Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use www.tweezerman.com and any other websites, social media platforms including, without limitation Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest and Instagram and services that are owned and/or controlled by us (collectively, the “Website”). Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how Tweezerman International, LLC (“Company”, “we,” or “us”) collects and uses the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Website and our products and services.

###### Your Consent

By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what limited circumstances, if ever, we disclose it. Continued access or use of our Website shall constitute your express acceptance of any modifications to this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy does not cover information that you submit on other websites, even if we communicate with you on those sites. For example, if you post something on Facebook, Twitter, or YouTube, that information is governed by the privacy policies on those websites, and is not governed by this policy.

###### What Information Do We Collect?

When you visit our Website you may provide us with two types of information: Personal Information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Website. "Personal Information" is information that can be used to identify you (whether alone or in combination), such as your first and last name, email address, zip code/post code, billing address, shipping address, phone number, payment card information, age, and any other information you choose to provide.

We engage third parties, such as Google’s Analytics to provide analytics about the use of our Website. These entities may use cookies, web beacons, pixels, embedded scripts, and other technologies to automatically collect information about your use of the Website, such as your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information.

###### Email Information

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

###### How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

Broadly speaking, we use Personal Information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Website, new products and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at the address listed below.

###### What Are Cookies?

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it.

Note that your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “Do Not Track” signal to sites and online services you visit. There is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. Like many websites and online services, we currently do not alter our practices when we receive a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” you may wish to visit http://www.allaboutdnt.com.

###### How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?

As you browse or shop on our Website, the Website uses its cookies to differentiate you from other shoppers so your shopping cart is only available to you. In some cases, we may use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Website server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Website and which parts of the Website are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Website and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

###### Notice of New Services and Changes

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by sending us an email at the address listed below.

###### Children

Our Website is intended for a general audience and not directed to children under 13 years of age. We do not intend to collect personal information as defined by the U.S. Children’s Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) (“Children’s Personal Information”) in a manner that is not permitted by COPPA, and for any children’s or mixed-use portions of our Website (if any) we will comply with COPPA. If you are a parent or guardian and believe we have collected Children’s Personal Information in a manner not permitted by COPPA, please contact us at by sending a letter to the address listed below (Attention: Legal) and we will remove such data to the extent required by COPPA.

Parents may want to consider commercially available parental control protections to limit what minors can access online and/or monitor their minor children’s online activities. Examples include: www.netnanny.com; www.webwatcher.com and www.sentrypc.com. We do not endorse these or other services and are not responsible for them.

###### Data Security

We take reasonable steps to have physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in place to help protect your Personal Information. This may include, in appropriate circumstances, use of Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) encryption. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information collected through our Website.

###### Contact Us

We are always interested in what our customers have to say. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at:

Tweezerman International, LLC  
2 Tri Harbor Court  
Port Washington, NY 11050  
info@tweezerman.com  
1(800)645-3340
